https://normans-rare-guitars.reverbsites.com/pages/privacy

18969 VENTURA BLVD. TARZANA, CA 91356
(818) 344-8300ELECTRICACOUSTICBASSESAMPSMERCHVIDEOSABOUTCONTACTPODCAST *new*CELEBRITIESPRIVACYProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.normansrareguitars.com and Norman’s Rare Guitars and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Norman’s Rare Guitars include www.normansrareguitars.com and NRG. The NRG website is a E-Commerce site. By using the NRG website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
NRG may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase NRG’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. NRG may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your gender. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NRG. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NRG website.
NRG encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from NRG so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. NRG is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the NRG website.
Use of your Personal Information
NRG collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
NRG may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NRG and its affiliates. NRG may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
NRG does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
NRG may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NRG, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
NRG may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NRG, in order to determine what NRG services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NRG to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
NRG will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NRG or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NRG; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NRG, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The NRG website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NRG pages, or register with NRG site or services, a cookie helps NRG to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NRG website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NRG features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NRG services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, NRG uses the following:
Comodo
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
NRG does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Disconnecting your NRG Account from Third Party Websites
You will be able to connect your NRG account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR NRG ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. You may modify your login API settings at any time by logging into your account and select the connections tab..
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from NRG by contacting us here:
– Web page: _________________
– Email: _________________
– Phone: _________________
Changes to this Statement
NRG will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. NRG encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NRG is protecting your information.
Contact Information
NRG welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NRG has not adhered to this Statement, please contact NRG at:
Norman’s Rare Guitars
18969 Ventura Blvd.
